ritecounter.com 2010-11-28

# 

**We Respect your Privacy**  

Any personal information you provide to us including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of RiteCounter.

For each visitor to our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes your computer IP Address, Operating System, Browser and referrer.

The information we collect is used to improve our services.

 **External Sites**  

RiteCounter is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information to them.

 **Cookies**  

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows RiteCounter to recognize you each time you visit our site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and RiteCounter does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as Google Ads, Yahoo! Ads or MSN Ad where available.

 **Complaints about privacy**  

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to RiteCounter and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through RiteCounter have separate data and privacy practices independent of ours.

If you have any complaints relating to RiteCounter online privacy policy, please notify us by using the contact form. While RiteCounter accepts no liability for any third party material or links posted or advertise on our site, we will investigate all complaints.
